噢  一个包裹
Ooh! A package.
等一下  里面是什 么 一件新衣服
Wait, what's in it? a new blouse?
一个新包包
A new bag?
还是那种短到都拉不过腰的性感内衣
Underwear that doesn't go all the way up to your waist?
这是个古董级的搓衣板
It is an antique washboard.
哦  真是个漂亮的玩意啊
Oh! isn't she a beaut?
它将会帮助
It's going to help
玛蒂和我赢得这个周末的杰瑟普拓荒者寻踪
Maddie and me win the mother-daughter challenge
母女挑战赛
At jessup's pioneer trail this weekend.
呃  不就是那个我以前
Ugh! is that that woodsy place
和玛蒂去郊游的那个
That Maddie and I used to go to on field trips
最大的特色在于上厕所的时候
Where the highlight was going to the bathroom
要坐在圆木上的深山老林么
While sitting on a log?
对头  玛蒂和我已经连续四年
Yep! Maddie and I have been doing this challenge
参加这个挑战赛了
For the last four years.
你只要在树林中搭帐篷
You camp in the woods
体验着和十九世纪先人们一样的生活
And live like people did in the 1800s.
你这是造了什么孽啊
Are you being punished?
其中最成功的母女组合
The most successful mother-daughter team
将会赢得金色的奶油搅拌器
Wins the golden butter churn
并且在其他的女同胞面前耀武扬威
And gets to lord it over the other ladies
整整一年
For the entire year.
只不过现在金搅子还是一幅照片
Yeah, this is just a picture
因为我和我妈并没赢过
'cause mom and I have never really won it.
对啊  我们中总有一个在拿够胜利点之前
Well, one of us always seems to get leprosy
被裁定为得了麻风病
Or fall into a wolverine nest
- 或是掉到了狼窝里头  - 对的
- before we get enough points. - yeah.
我们中的一个  指的是玛蒂
And by one of us, I mean maddie.
- 妈  - 怎么了
- mom. - hmm?
我可以看得到听得到你
I can see and hear you.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
呃  这不会是你又要拖着我去的
Ugh! this isn't going to be one of those things
那一堆破事吧
That you drag me to, is it?
我们笑个啥呢
Why are we laughing?
我跟着你去有什么好笑的
What's so funny about me going with you?
你到底要不要邀请我
Are you inviting me or not?
丽芙  这是脏兮兮苦哈哈的野外生存
Liv, this is rough-and-tumble outdoorsy living.
我们当然不会邀请你了
Of course we're not inviting you.
她胆敢不邀请我
How dare she not invite me.
当然了  这活动听起来
Sure, it sounds gross
又恶心又脏兮兮的又愚蠢
And dirty and stupid,
但是她好歹要问问我啊
But she should have at least asked.
这样我就可以严词拒绝
Then I could have turned her down
并且嘲笑她了
And laughed in her face.
算了吧  你一天都撑不过去的
No, you wouldn't survive a day.
最好的朋友
better in stereo
不同的朋友
b-- b-- better in stereo
迎着清晨阳光
- I'm up with the sunshine - let's go
穿上舒服衣裳
- I lace up my high tops - oh no
扣篮  热热身
slam dunk, ready or not
秀出你的份量
yeah, show me what you got
站在舞台中央
- I'm under the spotlight - holler
准备下一场较量
I dare you, come on and follow
你有你的节拍
you dance to your own beat
我的歌声嘹亮
i'll sing the melody
你想接受
when you say yea-ah-ah
我却摇头
I say no-oh-oh
你想停留
when you say stop
我却一心只想  走走走
all I want to do is go go go
你  我最好的朋友
you you, the other half of me me
学不来的朋友
the half i'll never be-e
截然不同的朋友
the half that drives me crazy
你  我最好的朋友
you you, the better half of me me
离不开的朋友
the half i'll always need
你我有
but we both know
不或缺的朋友
we're better in stereo.
妈妈  妈妈
Mom. mom. mom.
我逮着午餐食材了
I caught lunch.
是什么
What is it?
我不清楚  抓捕的过程发生的太快了
I don't know. it all went down pretty quick.
维克菲尔德女士
Mrs. wakefield.
给我们记上分吧
Put us on the scoreboard.
看起来鲁尼队
Looks like team rooney
今年干劲十足啊
Are the eager beavers this year.
那是故意说的俏皮话
Nature pun intended.
玛蒂
Maddie!
我来参加母女活动周啦
I am here for the mother-daughter weekend!
猜猜谁将要参加拓荒者聚会了啦
Who is ready to get their pioneer par-tay on?
噢  亲  你来这儿干什么啊
Oh, honey, what are you doing here?
我还以为这活动不适合你呢
I thought this wasn't your kind of thing.
对啊  再说了  我和妈妈都已经
Yeah, and besides, mom and I are already
组合好母女双人的一队了
Doing this together and it's only teams of two.
这就是为什么我出去凑了一个妈妈
That's why I went out and rustled up a mom.
一个妈妈
A mom?
你到底在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
哦  我指的是布丽·都蒙德
Oh, I'm just talking about Bree du Monde.
布丽
Bree?
布丽·都蒙德是在《放声高歌》里饰演
Bree du Monde is the actress who played my mom
我妈妈的演员
On “Sing it Loud!"
她可是个三面手
She's a triple threat--
华丽的外表  前卫的时尚品味  疯狂的摇滚性格
Gor-gene, fab-smash, and rock-a-diculous.
哦  她来了
Oh! there she is now.
拓荒者布丽  听候大草原的指示
Pioneer Bree, reporting to the prairie.
哦 忘记把坐骑锁上了
Oops, forgot to lock my horse.
好了  小伙子
Okay, buddy--
女同胞们都去露营了
Womenfolk are out camping.
老爹去打高尔夫了
Dad is out golfing.
这就意味着我们有一整天
And that means we have all day
来为所欲为了
To do whatever we want.
早就意识到了  哥们
Way ahead of you, dude.
不然我怎么会用脚来吃排骨呢
Why do you think I'm eating a rib with my foot?
简直让我印象深刻啊
As impressed with that as I am...
我有更大的计划
I've got bigger plans.
你是指用脚吃鸡腿么
You mean like eating a drumstick with my foot.
得了吧  伙计  我说的是
Okay, buddy, I am talking about
一个赚一大笔外快的好方法
A way to make cold, hard cash.
你抓住了我的注意力
You have my full attention.
别把这机会浪费了
Don't waste this moment.
丽芙·鲁尼住宅游
Liv Rooney residential tour--
只花一小笔钱  当地的《放声歌唱》粉丝俱乐部的成员们
For a small fee, members of the local "Sing it Loud!" fan club
就可以看到他们最爱的青少年偶像
Can see where their favorite teen idol
生活起居的地方
Eats, sleeps, and obsessively flosses.
我一直在收集她的用完的洗发水瓶子
I've been collecting her empty shampoo bottles
和剪下来的脚趾甲
And toenail clippings.
你能再搞个礼品店么
Can you say "gift shop"?
我就知道靠你这点精灵古怪
I knew i'd cash in on how creepy you were
能赚大钱
One of these days.
把你脚上的酱汁擦干净
Wipe that sauce off your foot.
住宅游再过一小时就开始了
The tour shows up in an hour.
嘿 同志们
Hey, guys.
高尔夫泡汤了
Golf got canceled.
真是倒霉催了
Bummer for me.
但是我们能一起度过这周末了
But we get to spend the weekend together now
享受一下父子增进感情的好时间
For a little father-son bonding time.
太好了
Yay.
那么现在玛蒂去剥树皮吃了
So while maddie's off skinning lunch...
我们干嘛不来叙叙旧呢
Why don't we catch up?
布丽  你不跟我说一下就来
Bree, it is so good of you to come
协助丽芙真是太好了
And support Liv on such short notice.
好的  凯伦
Well, karen,
当我的电视里的女儿打来电话
When my tv daughter called,
我就立马放下手头的一切赶来了
I just canceled everything on my schedule to be here.
也就是那些值得我
Just one of those situations
搭个做老娘的架子的事
Where I had to drop a butt bomb of mom on it.
搭个做老娘的架子
"drop a butt bomb of mom on it"
曾经是我的口头禅
Is something I used to say.
布丽听见了  结果就给她的电视角色抢去了
Bree heard it and turned it into her tv character's catchphrase.
自从那时  她就靠这发大财了
Since then, she's made a fortune
给烹饪书搭了个做老娘的架子
Dropping a butt bomb of mom on cookbooks,
锻炼视频  和让你青春永驻的酸奶
Workout videos, and yogurt that keeps you young.
我就此没有用过这句话
I haven't said it since.
好怀念啊
I really miss the butt bomb.
那么  妈妈
Well, mom--
- 咋了  亲爱的  - 啥事  甜心
- yeah, sugar? - what, sweetie?
噢...
Oh...
噢  天啊
Oh, wow!
这还真是尴尬啊  对不
This is awkward, isn't it?
我怎么没想到呢  呵呵
Hadn't really thought of that. ha ha!
之后我们要去搭帐篷
So we should probably go set up our tent.
然后我们在篝火边上见吧  凯伦女士
And I'll see you around the campfire, Karen?
好了  我们要赶快想辙打发掉老爸
All right, we have got to think fast.
来参加丽芙鲁尼住宅游的妹子们
The girls coming for the Liv Rooney residential tour
随时都会到
Will be here any minute,
而老爹表现得像他是这儿的老大一样
And dad is acting like he owns the place.
他貌似确实是啊
He sort of does.
我们需要一个能让
We need a project
老爹忙得不可开交的计划
That will keep dad busy.
你干啥呢  你知道老妈对垃圾粉碎机的严格规定的
You know how strict mom is about what goes in the disposal.
这么做会弄坏它的
That's gonna break it.
原来如此  快塞进去
Shove it in.
全都塞进去
Shove it all in.
爸 垃圾粉碎机好像坏了
Dad! something's wrong with the disposal.
快来修好它啊
You need to fix it.
这太妙了
This is perfect.
你知道吧  老爹一直是干什么事
You know how dad takes forever
都干到不知猴年马月的
To do pretty much anything.
你做了什么啊
What'd you do?
你知道老妈对垃圾粉碎机的严格规定的
You know how strict your mom is about what goes in the disposal.
这下好了
Yep.
这堵得死死的
It's jammed up real good.
但你还是能修好的  对不  爹地
You can fix it, though-- right, dad?
当然能了  我们的爸爸是个铁血真男儿啊
Of course he can. our father's a man's man.
他什么都能修好的
He can fix anything.
说对了  看来皮特叔叔要施展
Yeah, looks like it's time for pete
通管子的老身手了
To get his old plumber on.
欢迎光临 丽芙的粉丝们
Greetings, lovers of liv
和喜欢鲁尼家的人们
And all things rooney.
欢迎来到
Welcome
丽芙·鲁尼住宅游
To the Liv Rooney residential tour.
和礼品店
And gift shop.
我们必须要保持警惕  别打搅了
We must be very careful not to disturb
住宅里的其他成员
Any of the other residents.
来起步走
And we're walking.
继续向前走
这赚钱简直是易如反
It's like taking candy from a--
亚蒂
Artie.
抱歉我来晚了
Oh, my late arrivals.
欢迎来到地球上最美妙的地方
Welcome to the best place on earth--
昔日
The past.
上缴你们所有现代物品的时间到了
Time to turn in all modern-day devices.
噢  妈呀
Oh, dear.
呃...
Um...
你所说的“现代”到底是什么意思呢
So exactly how like "modern" are we talking?
因为我的手机已经挺老了
'cause, I mean, my phone's pretty old.
我想我大概是六个月前买的吧
I think i've had it for at least like six months.
可是拓荒者们没有手机  你也不能有
Well, if the pioneers didn't have it, neither can you.
哦对了  别忘了上缴你们的梳子
Oh, and don't forget your hairbrushes.
我们是拓荒者  又不是动物
We're pioneers, not animals.
开疆时代的妇女们会自己削多余的柴禾
On the frontier women would whittle hair-grooming tools
来制造梳头工具
Made out of leftover firewood.
梳子拿好不谢
Here's a comb.
我的宝贝们啊
My babies.
别担心  亲爱的
Don't worry, sugar.
每个人都是有值钱玩意的
Everyone has their price.
嘿 我用“老妈架子圣诞节”的签名照
How about I trade you that curling iron
换你的卷发棒怎么样
For a signed copy of "a very butt bomb christmas"?
哦 丽芙 我们要谈谈
Oh, liv, honey. we should talk.
我开始怀疑你是不是因为我没邀请你而不高兴了
I'm starting to wonder if you're upset that I didn't invite you.
你怎么可能会这么想呢
Why ever would you think that?
你从国家的另外一边
You brought in a substitute mom
带来了个冒牌妈妈
From the other side of the country.
这不是个明显的信号么
It's kind of a red flag.
哦  也许你是对的  妈妈
Oh, yeah, maybe you're right, mom.
也许我确实有点不高兴
Maybe I am a little bit upset.
也许我现在要在你的比赛里打败你了
Maybe now I will beat you at your own game.
引用拓荒者们的话就是
As the pioneers would say,
愿君祥瑞
I bid you good day.
这改变不了什么
This changes nothing!
这边走  妹子们
Right this way, ladies.
现在往左看  这次游览的重头戏
And now to our left, the highlight of the tour.
丽芙·鲁尼的闺房
Liv rooney's sleeping chamber.
请不要越过房间属于丽芙的那头
Please do not disturb liv's side of the room.
但是没啥名气的她双胞胎的床就随便站
But feel free to stand on the un-famous twin's bed
还能照张相
And take a picture.
这和我想象的别无二致
It's exactly how I imagined it.
当代的都市公主啊
Urban princess contemporary.
花多少钱能让我过了这条鹅绒围栏
How much to get me past the velvet rope?
抱歉  亚蒂
Sorry, Artie.
这是禁止入内的
That is off-limits.
10 美元
10 bucks.
能让我享受一下明星风范的话给你 20 美元
I'll give you 20 if I can have a diva moment.
成交
Deal.
我很想开开眼
I really want to see this.
你确定这是个好主意么
Are you sure this is a good idea?
帕克  我认为这一切都不是个好主意
Parker, I'm not sure any of this is a good idea.
预备
Ready?
丽芙与亚蒂要白头偕老
Liv and artie forever!
我实在是太想取笑一下了
I really want to make fun of that.
但是那确实是才气不浅啊
But it was nothing short of magnificent.
我们已经努力了三个小时了
We have been at this for three hours.
搅拌奶油到底要多长时间啊
How long does it take to churn butter?
很明显至少要花三个小时
Well, obviously it takes at least three hours!
我很抱歉  布丽  我只是
I'm sorry, Bree, I just...
我真的很想要那些树皮做的项链玩意儿
I really want one of those bark necklace thingies.
好了  我们来看看
Okay, let's check.
哈  哈  给你们看看  女士们
Ha ha! in yo face, ladies!
你 你看见那个了 对不
You-- you saw that, right?
我们还能够记上分么
We're still going to get credit for that?
不能
No.
但是伐木比赛又诞生了一个赢家哦
But we do have a winner in the wood-chopping competition.
祝贺鲁尼队
Congratulations, team rooney!
太好了
Yes!
伐木的秘诀就是痛恨那块木头
The secret is to really hate the wood.
妈
Mom.
今年终于属于我们了
This is finally our year.
我的意思是  我们这么领先
I mean, we are so far ahead,
都已经拿定那个金搅子了
We've got that golden butter churn all locked up.
但是  除非我们干了什么傻事
Well, unless we do something dumb--
我说的我们  是指你  所以最好什么都别碰
And by we, I mean you-- so don't touch anything.
嘿  听着你说呢  妈妈
Hey, I hear you, mom.
所以这里
So here...
就是通往金搅子的大道
Is to the golden butter churn.
玛蒂·鲁尼
Maddie rooney.
你是不是刚刚喝了一口又绵又滑的白水
Did you just take a nice, long drink of water
来防止脱水呢
To avoid dehydration?
对的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
那么你就死掉啦
Then you're dead.
呃 什么 这
Uh-- wha-- uh...
等一下 先别
Wait, hold on.
我煮沸了这水啊
I boiled this water.
不不不不  你煮的是那桶水
No no no no. you boiled that water.
啧啧
Oops!
但我们今年势在必得啊
But we were going to win this year.
把死人抬出去
Bringing out the dead!
这  不  妈妈  我都是很小心的
Wha-- no, mom, I have been so careful.
你懂得  我们那么领先
You know what-- we are so far ahead,
你单枪匹马就能把金搅子赢回来
You win that golden butter churn for both of us!
你要让梦想成真啊
You keep this dream alive!
把尸体准备展览吧
Let's prepare the body for the viewing.
奇异恩典
amazing grace
何等
how sweet...
之后丽芙的角色就说
And then Liv's character was like,
哦不  你可没这么干
"oh, no, you didn't!"
之后那个坏女孩就说
And then the bad girl was like,
哦是的  我就这么干了
"oh, yes, I did."
之后她们怒气冲冲的来了一场舞蹈比赛
And then they had an angry dance-off.
就像是
It was like--
亚蒂  亚蒂  亚蒂  亚蒂
Artie. artie. artie! artie!
你够了
That is enough.
下床去
Get off the bed.
好吧
Fine.
之后她们化解恩怨  成了对好朋友
And then they made up and became best friends.
好了 同志们
All right, people.
请把注意力集中到窗台上
Please direct your attention to the window seat,
你们能看到很多丽芙
Where you will find every stuffed animal
从小到大玩过的毛绒玩具
Liv has ever played with.
这些都是可供购买的
Also available for purchase.
我还要花钱买那些我送她的吗
Do I have to pay for the ones I gave her?
你只要不把从她桌子底下
I'm not answering that question
抠来的口香糖吐出来
Until you've returned the gum
我就不回答你的提问
You took from under her desk.
嘿  孩子们  你们在楼上么
Hey, boys, you up there?
老爸来了  大家快躲起来
Dad's coming. everybody hide!
我指的是躲到鞋橱里
I mean, to the shoe closet.
好了  同志们
All right, people.
起步转移  继续转移
And we're moving. and we're moving.
转移速度快点
And we're moving faster.
都赶快躲进去啊
So that means move faster.
嘿  你们俩在丽芙和玛蒂的房间里干嘛
Hey, what are you doing in Liv and maddie's room?
我们只是太想念她们了
We just miss them so much.
还有那堆阁楼里的毛绒玩具是怎么回事
And why are their stuffed animals down from the attic?
我们也太想念它们了
We missed them too.
那台垃圾粉碎机彻底坏了
Well, the garbage disposal's fried.
我要去五金店买一台新的
I have to go to the hardware store to get a new one.
果然  你确实是铁血真男儿啊
Yeah, you're a real man's man.
我先离开一会儿
I'll see you later.
对了  帮我个忙
Hey, do me a favor.
把那些毛绒玩具都放回阁楼
Put those stuffed animals back in the attic.
它们挺吓人的
They're creepy.
哦  谢谢帮忙挑水  丽芙
Oh, thanks for fetching the water, liv.
你错过了一个美好的早晨
You missed a wonderful wake.
好了  现在玛蒂那组已经出局了
Yeah, and now with Maddie out of the game,
我们也许真的有击败妈妈的好机会
We might actually have a chance at beating mom.
她没必要把所有的柴禾都
She did have to trade in all her firewood
换成葬花啊
For funeral flowers.
噢  布丽
Oh, Bree.
我真为我们感到骄傲
I am so proud of us.
我是说  一开始  我们无中生有
I mean, first, we create butter out of nothing
就制成了奶油
But thin air.
呃  好吧  五加仑的牛奶和三小时的苦工
Okay, well, five gallons of milk and three hours of labor,
但是仍然  我们制成了奶油
But still-- we made butter.
而现在我们要把衣服弄得
And now we are getting our clothes
一尘不染
Squeaky clean...
而不花分毫
With nothing...
除了脏石头
But dirty rocks...
和把我皮肤伤得不浅的肥皂
And soap that I'm pretty sure is burning my skin off.
让我自己这么说吧
And if I do say so myself,
我弄了把有老妈架子的
I have dropped a butt bomb
原木梳子
Of pioneer mom on this here log comb.
哎呀
Ow!
我其实休息了一小会
I actually took a little break
把我的脚丫子放到溪水里
And cooled my toes off in the stream,
然后提神到让我的脚像被刺了一样
And it was so refreshing that it made my feet tingle.
真是爽啊
You go, girl!
那是蚂蟥吗
Are those leeches?
蚂蟥  活生生的蚂蟥
Leeches! real, live leeches!
快把那些吸血鬼弄走啊
Get these bloodsucking slugs off of me!
布丽  别愣着不动
Bree, do something!
快放开她  蚂蟥们
Get off her, leeches!
快走  快走
Shoo! shoo!
得了吧  布丽
Come on, Bree.
这就是你该搭个老妈架子的地方
This is where you drop a butt bomb of mom on it.
哦  宝贝  我又不是你亲妈
Oh, honey, I'm not your mom.
别做傻事哦
Don't take this the wrong way.
我先走一步了
But I'm out of here.
难道还有不傻的事可做吗
Is there a right way to take that?
我们游览的终点站是
And as we conclude the tour...
吼吼吼  这个景点太稀有了
Ooh hoo hoo, this is a rare sight.
丽芙·鲁尼的亲爹啊
Liv rooney's real-life father.
别打扰他
Don't disturb him.
我们从后门出去
We'll go out the back.
才没门呢
No way.
我买的是全票
I was promised a full tour.
我的贺卡上要印上我在这里
My holiday card will have a picture of me
每个房间拍的照片
In every room in this house.
好吧
Fine.
请稍等片刻
Just wait here one second.
顺便说一句  我恨死你了
Also, I hate you.
你好啊  老爸
Hey, pops.
你在忙乎什么呢
Whatcha up to?
我去五金店的时候
While I was at the hardware store,
顺便买了个报警系统
I picked up an alarm system.
我们家里有个大明星
We have a celebrity living in this house.
会有人花钱来参观的
People would pay to get in here.
赞  给我好好讲讲吧
Fascinating. show me everything.
别将目光从操作板上移开
Don't take your eyes off this box.
我从来没像今天这样对你在干的活这么感兴趣
I've never been more interested in anything you've ever done.
别动啊  乔伊
Hold still, joey.
我在设置动作探测器
I'm setting the motion detector.
任何动作都会触发报警器
Any movement will trip the alarm.
警报启动
Alarm activated.
检测到 12 个入侵者
12 intruders detected.
这到底是什么破玩意
What's wrong with this thing?
呃  我知道咋回事了
Well-- well, I know.
我太激动了  动作根本停不下来
Just so excited I can't stand still.
警报取消
Alarm deactivated.
屋内安全
house secure.
我好像之前跟你们说过把那些吓人的玩意
I thought I told you to put those creepy things
放回到阁楼里去
Back up in the attic.
我记得我好像放过了
I thought I did.
你总不会认为它们是自己闹鬼走到这里来的吧
You don't think they came down on their own, do you?
当我放声高唱
if I sing about leeches
蚂蟥就会自行退散
maybe they'll go away, la la la
啦啦啦啦啦啦蚂蟥退散了
la la la la la la leeches!
快走掉啊  蚂蟥们
Get off me, leeches.
我刚看见布丽顺着大路一边叫一边跑我就知道你出事了
I just saw Bree running and screaming down the trail.
呃  我不明白你为何会这么想
Well, I can't imagine why you would think that.
我简直是好的不得了啊
I have never been better.
我被蚂蝗叮上了  妈  我腿上都是蚂蟥
I have leeches, mom. i've got the leeches.
哦  对  你确实腿上都是蚂蟥
Oh, yes, you have leeches.
但是  你很幸运
Well, lucky for you,
每个好妈妈都会随身携带信用卡
Every good mom keeps a credit card handy
来预防紧急情况
In case of an emergency.
呃
Ugh.
这是另一个喜爱信用卡的理由啊
Yet another reason to love credit cards.
当年的女性是不会有信用卡的
Pioneer women did not carry credit cards.
你被取消资格了
You are disqualified.
请交出你的软帽吧
Please surrender your bonnet.
哦  不  妈妈
Oh, no, mom!
你的软帽发型太可怕了
You have horrible bonnet-head.
她说的没错
Oh, she's not wrong.
你看起来跟头野牛似的
You look like a bison.
那么 丽芙
Well, liv,
你是鲁尼家最后一个还在坚持的了
You are the last Rooney standing.
我对你骄傲极了
I couldn't be prouder of you.
你是我们中把金搅子
You're our last chance
带回家的最后希望了
To bring home the golden butter churn.
我才不在乎什么破金搅子呢
I don't care about some stupid golden butter churn.
我只是想和我的妈妈多呆呆
I just wanted to spend time with my mom.
哦 谢谢了
Oh, thank you.
你口中的妈妈指的是我  对吧
You are talking about me, right?
我想我只是有点嫉妒
I guess I just got a little bit jealous
你和玛蒂的母女时刻罢了
With all of you and maddie's mother-daughter time,
我也想拥有一些
And I just wanted some for me.
顺带一提  我可从没玛蒂的腿上刮过蚂蟥
I never scraped leeches off of maddie's legs.
谢谢你照顾我
Thanks for taking care of me.
你才是个实打实的好妈妈
You are one butt bomb of mom.
我终于把这老娘的架子给夺回来了
Mama got her butt bomb back.
砰 搭好了
Boom! dropped.
你们不会知道洗个澡是多爽的
You have no idea how good it feels to be clean.
你要加力擦洗
You have to work extra hard
才能把蚂蟥的粘液从你指头上洗掉
To scrub leech slime off of your fingers.
欢迎回家 妈妈
Well, welcome home, mom.
当你出门的时候
While you were away,
爸爸干了些很男子汉的事情
Dad did some manly things.
包括升级了你的垃圾粉碎机
Including upgrading your garbage disposal.
- 你是不是把它弄坏了  - 别跑题了
- you broke it, didn't you? - not the point.
皮特 你确定你知道
Pete, are you sure you know how
怎么安装垃圾粉碎机么
To install a garbage disposal?
别跑题了
Not the point.
你应该试试  用的可顺手了
You should try it. it works great.
我们把冰箱里连帕克都不吃的剩菜
We tested it with all the leftovers in the fridge
都拿来做测试了
That we couldn't even get parker to eat.
这就是为什么我对丢进粉碎机
This is why we have strict rules
的剩饭剩菜有严规戒律
About what goes into the disposal.
我不得不佩服你 哥们
I got to hand it to you, munch.
你想出来了个疯狂的主意
You came up with a ridiculous idea
而且让它还奏效了
And you made it work.
最好的是压根没人发现
The best part is nobody found out.
你们俩干的事被我发现了
You two are so busted.
太对不住了  我们本该
We're sorry. we should--
你到底知道了些什么
What do you know?
噢  你们直接侵犯了我的地盘
Oh, just that you completely space-invaded me.
如果你们要拿我最爱的梳子
If you are going to use my favorite hairbrush
去梳小丑的假发
To brush out a clown wig,
至少要刷完后把恶心的橙色头发
At least remove the nasty orange hair
都清除掉
When you're done.
对的 被你发现了
Yeah, you got us.
我们确实偷了你的梳子去梳小丑的假发套
We were stealing brushes and combing clown wigs
梳了一整个周末
All weekend.
真是火眼金睛啊
Totally busted.
千万别在这么干了
Just don't let it happen again.
给你 20 美元  帮我把那梳子弄到手
I'll give you 20 bucks if you can get me that brush.